{
    "subject": "resource/Casper_and_the_Angels",
    "predicate": "property/episodenumber",
    "object": "7",
    "human_readable": "Casper and the Angels is episode number 7.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8633319735527039,
            "question": "What episode number is Casper and the Angels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7015676498413086,
            "question": "Is Casper and the Angels a popular episode?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6227927803993225,
            "question": "What is the name of the episode that is number 7?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6069670915603638,
            "question": "What happens in the episode Casper and the Angels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6028156280517578,
            "question": "Are there other episodes related to Casper and the Angels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5621997117996216,
            "question": "What genre is the episode Casper and the Angels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5266913771629333,
            "question": "What makes Casper and the Angels a memorable episode?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39638182520866394,
            "question": "Does episode number 7 have a special significance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38356584310531616,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Casper and the Angels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33881765604019165,
            "question": "Why is episode number 7 important?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Casper and the Angels is episode number 7.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1317_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main characters in Casper and the Angels?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1317_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does episode number 7 have a special significance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1317_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Casper and the Angels a memorable episode?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1317_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1317_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because there is no information in the provided context that explicitly states Casper and the Angels is episode number 7. The documents do provide a list of all the \"Casper and the Angels\" episodes, but it does not include a numbering or ranking system that would allow us to determine which one is episode number 7."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not contain any information about episodes of \"Casper and the Angels\" being numbered. The documents describe the show's content, characters, and run time but do not specify an episode number like 7."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}